<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SensorProject</string>

    <string-array name="roomList">
        <item>Current room</item>
        <item>Other room</item>
        <item>+ add new room</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="mRoomView">3.136 Building A</string>


    <string name="mUsername">Username</string>
    <string name="mPassword">Password</string>

    <string name="mLoginButton">Login</string>




    <string name="mSignUpLink">Sign up</string>
    <string name="mForgotPasswordLink">Forgot password</string>
    <string name="mLoginRememberCheckBox">Remember me</string>

    <string name="mCoView">CO</string>
    <string name="mTempView">Temperature</string>
    <string name="mHumidView">Humidity</string>

    <string name="mCoInput"></string>
    <string name="mTempInput"></string>
    <string name="mHumidInput"></string>


    //The gauges clicked

    <string name="temperatureInfo">Optimal range: 21-25, for our best performance. If it becomes too hot or cold
    we begin to loose concentration. The reason for a drop in concentration, is because of the energy that
        is used by our bodies in trying to make us warmer or cooler.
        Less energy therefore goes into helping you concentrate.</string>


    <string name="humidityInfo">
        Optimal range: 45-55%.
         Naturally, when our bodies start to heat up, we release sweat. This sweat is then evaporated from the skin, which in turn, helps to cool us off.
When the air has a high moisture content, as is the case in humid weather, this sweat cannot evaporate,
         leaving our bodies feeling hot and sticky.
        To cool off, our bodies must work even harder.
        This results in excessive sweating,
        increased rate and depth of blood circulation and increased respiration.
        Excessive sweating can cause a loss of water and chemicals that the body
        needs in order to function properly, potentially putting our health in jeopardy.
        According to the American Society of Heating, Refrigerating and Air-Conditioning Engineers (ASHRAE),
        the ideal humidity range for humans is between 30 to 60 percent relative humidity.
        The ideal is somewhere around 45-55%. Very high levels of humidity contribute to the growth of mold,
        funguses, dust mites, and other pests. Mold contributes to a number of diseases and thrives in humid
        climates, generally above 60 percent humidity. For people suffering from asthma and other respiratory
        disorders, humidity should not exceed 50 percent, as high humidity can aggravate symptoms.
        Dry or itchy skin conditions are aggravated by low humidity, which tends to dry out the skin.</string>

    <string name="coInfo">Optimal Range: 1 to 70 ppm. Breathing CO can cause headache, dizziness, vomiting, and nausea. If CO levels are high enough, you may become unconscious or die. Exposure to moderate and high levels of CO over long periods of time has also been linked with increased risk of heart disease. People who survive severe CO poisoning may suffer long-term health problems.
    The health effects of CO depend on the CO concentration and length of exposure, as well as each individual's health condition. CO concentration is measured in parts per million (ppm). Most people will not experience any symptoms from prolonged exposure to CO levels of approximately 1 to 70 ppm but some heart patients might experience an increase in chest pain. As CO levels increase and remain above 70 ppm, symptoms become more noticeable and can include headache, fatigue and nausea. At sustained CO concentrations above 150 to 200 ppm, disorientation, unconsciousness, and death are possible.
</string>


    <string name="mShowButton">Show</string>
    <string name="mChartButton">Click for work</string>
    <string name="logoView"></string>


    <string-array name="ranges">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>70</item>
        <item>80</item>
        <item>90</item>
        <item>100</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="information_text">If CO is too high, it becomes dangerous and will decrease focus and oxygen levels</string>


</resources>
